dollspace.com 2009-12-27

# DollSpace - Privacy Policy

| 

DollSpace takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how DollSpace treats personal information that DollSpace collects and receives, including information related to your past use of DollSpace products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.   

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DollSpace does not own or control, or to people that DollSpace does not employ or pay.  

**Information Collection and Use**  

  * DollSpace collects personal information when you register with DollSpace, when you use DollSpace products or services, and when you visit DollSpace pages of the pages of certain DollSpace partners. DollSpace also collects information about you and your use of the web site that is not personal.  
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender. Once you register with DollSpace and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * DollSpace collects information about your transactions with us.  

  * DollSpace may collect information about your transactions with our business affiliates, including information about your use of products offered through the website.  

  * DollSpace automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, DollSpace cookie information, and the page you request.   

  * DollSpace may use some or all of your information for the following general purposes: to customize the user experience, to customize advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to offer customized features, to improve our services, to contact you, and to conduct research.  

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * DollSpace may share your non-personal information with affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-affiliates for commercial purposes. However, DollSpace does not provide personal contact information to third parties, other than as specified below, without your permission.  

  * DollSpace may also collect information about you from other sources, such as blogs and instant messaging services, and other users of DollSpace services in order to allow DollSpace and its affiliates, vendors, advertisers and other non-affiliates to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.  

  * Be aware that posting personal information on public areas of the DollSpace site (via Profile, Forums, Blogs, etc.) will make your information publicly available. Do not post information in public areas that you want to keep private. Also be aware that certain information you post or share with third parties like your friends or members of your network about yourself may be shared with other users and all such sharing of information is done at your own risk.  

  * DollSpace does not rent or sell personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:   
o We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
o We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations or suspected violations of DollSpace's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.   

**Cookies**

  * DollSpace may set and access DollSpace cookies on your computer to customize the user experience. You may realize certain losses of functionality if you turn your cookies off in your browser.   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * DollSpace may update this policy. We will announce significant changes in the way we treat personal information by posting prominently on the web site. However, you assume the responsibility of periodically reviewing this policy.   

|   
---|---|---
